beautybrands.com 2018-10-12

# Privacy and Security | Beauty Brands

  * What information does beautybrands.com protect?
  * How beautybrands.com protects your information
  * How beautybrands.com uses your personal information
  * Does beautybrands.com share any information it collects with outside parties?
  * How do I remove my address from the beautybrands.com mailing list?
  * What are cookies? How does beautybrands.com use cookies on the site?
  * Does beautybrands.com collect personal information for children under 13 years of age?
  * What does beautybrands.com do with submitted content?
  * What about links to other websites and services?
  * How do I consent to this privacy policy?
  * beautybrands.com Use of Web Beacons
  * Making a Purchase
  * How do I contact beautybrands.com about this privacy policy?
  * Security
  * License Information

**beautybrands.com** values its customers and respects their privacy. Customer information is collected in an effort to improve your online experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. **beautybrands.com** only communicates with you in regard to an order placed, or if you register to be notified of special deals or enter a contest or promotion on our website. We do not share, trade or sell your information to anyone outside of **beautybrands.com** without your prior consent. 

This Privacy Policy covers any personal information that **beautybrands.com** obtains from you when you use our website. We invite you to check back periodically to see if we have made any changes. If we make any material changes, we will post a notice on our homepage. By using our site, you agree to the terms of our policy. 

####  What information does **beautybrands.com** protect? 

We need to know your name, email address, mailing address, and credit card or debit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to our website, new **beauty brands** locations, services and special offers we think you might find valuable. 

####  How **beautybrands.com** protects your information? 

**beautybrands.com** realizes that our customers trust us to protect their personal information. We take that responsibility seriously. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. For example, we use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) authentication to protect the confidentiality of online transactions made on our site. SSL authentication and encryption of the information that you send to us over the internet help protect your online transaction information from third-party interception. 

We never display your full credit card number once it has been entered. We will only reveal the last four digits of your credit card for verification purposes. We urge you to protect your own privacy. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone or share your log-in information or password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Unfortunately, despite all of our efforts, there is always a risk that third parties may unlawfully intercept transmissions. This reality is true of all internet use. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit, and you transmit all information at your own risk.

####  How **beautybrands.com** uses your personal information 

**beautybrands.com** currently uses the personal information collected for correspondence, record keeping, order shipments, charges and activities on **beautybrands.com**. The information may also be used for the fulfillment of requested transactions and marketing. 

####  Does **beautybrands.com** share any information it collects with outside parties? 

**beautybrands.com** does not disclose any personal information collected to outside parties. **beautybrands.com** may retain outside parties to review certain personal information to advise on demographic and marketing issues. This is typically on an aggregated basis, and only done after such outside parties have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security and integrity of any personal information obtained. 

####  How does **beautybrands.com** use cookies on the site? 

"Cookies" are the small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We collect some anonymous information about how you use the site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our website, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave the website. The cookies track your computer, not you. They are not connected to any personal information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features on **beautybrands.com** , including placing items in your Shopping Bag and purchasing them. 

####  What does **beautybrands.com** do with submitted content? 

By submitting any photographs, video, reviews or any other material (the "Material") to **beauty brands** , you hereby acknowledge and agree to the following: By submitting to **beauty brands** any Material, you grant **beauty brands** the right to publish and otherwise use the Material throughout the world in any form or media for a period of one year following receipt by **beauty brands** of the Material. You have secured all permission necessary for the publishing of the Material in any form or media. 

If you are under 13 years of age, you must include written permission from your parents or legal guardian in order to have the Material published in any form of media by **beauty brands** , and the written permission of parents or legal guardians of other participants under 13 years of age in the Material. 

**beauty brands** shall be under no liability whatsoever to any participants in or other contributors to the Material, or to any third party arising out of the publishing of the Material. 

**beauty brands** shall have no obligation to publish the Material in any form of media. Furthermore, no warranty is given that the content of the Material published in any form of media will correspond in its entirety to any Material you have delivered to **beauty brands**. **beauty brands** shall be entitled to make any changes to the Material, as it deems fit. **beauty brands** shall not be obligated to return the Material to you at any time. 

**beauty brands** shall not be obligated to pay you a fee or compensate you any other way for the publishing of the Material. 

#### What about links to other websites and services?

**beautybrands.com** may link to other websites that are not under our control. These websites have their own privacy policies, which should be reviewed before submitting any personal information. **beautybrands.com** has no responsibility for linked websites and provides these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors. 

#### How do I consent to this privacy policy?

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by **beautybrands.com**. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

####  **beautybrands.com** Use of Web Beacons 

We have included web beacons on some of our web pages. **beautybrands.com** uses web beacons to transfer data (such as purchase and site usage history). **beautybrands.com** may provide this data to companies that assist **beautybrands.com** in data research and analysis: these companies are prohibited from using this data for any other purpose. The analysis and research helps **beautybrands.com** to determine customer preferences and improve **beautybrands.com** offerings. **beautybrands.com** may also rely upon third parties to assist with the use and implementation of the web beacons. 

Definition of web beacon: A web beacon, sometimes called a pixel, is a graphic image or small string of code that is included on web pages or in an email to enable the transfer of data. Web beacons can be used by companies for several purposes, such as reporting website traffic, customer preferences, advertising effectiveness, and general auditing.

#### Making a Purchase

When you buy something on **beautybrands.com** , you have to supply your billing address, phone number, shipping address and credit card or debit card information. By making a purchase, you become a registered user of **beautybrands.com**. You can choose to store information needed to make a purchase, such as your shipping and billing addresses, in the "my account" Profile page. If you change your mind about storing this information, you can amend or delete it by going to the relevant area of the "my account" Profile page and following the instructions. You can access this section using your registration password. 

#### Security

**beautybrands.com** has implemented Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology — one of the most robust encryption platforms available. 

Your credit card or debit card information will be encrypted from the moment you enter it. A browser in secure mode will display a URL beginning "https://" rather than the standard "http://." The "s" stands for "secure."

#### License Information

All **beauty brands** locations are licensed for all services in each respective state. Current license information is available at each store location and on **beautybrands.com**. View license information.
